Let's look at a basic model of an artificial neural network,
我们来看一个人工智能网络的基本模型
where we have only a single, hidden layer.
其中只包括一个单独的隐藏层
The inputs are each connected to the neurons in
每个输入都连接到隐藏层的神经元
the hidden layer and the neurons in the hidden layer are each
隐藏层的神经元都连接到
connected to the neurons in the output layer where
输出层的神经元
each neuron there represents a single output.
每个神经元表示一个单独的输出
We can look at it as a collection of mathematical functions.
我们可以把它看作数学函数的集合
Each input is connected mathematically to a hidden layer
从数学意义上来说 每个输入通过我们需要调整的一系列权重
of neurons through a set of weights we need to modify,
连接到包括神经元的隐藏层
and each hidden layer neuron is connected to the output layer in a similar way.
每个隐藏层的神经元也通过类似的方式连接到输出层
There is no limit to the number of inputs,
输入数量
number of hidden neurons in a layer,
隐藏神经元数量
and number of outputs,
和输出数量没有限制
nor are there any correlations between those numbers,
这些数字之间也没有联系
so we can have n inputs,
所以我们有 n 个输入
m hidden neurons, and k outputs.
m 个隐藏神经元和 k 个输出
In a closer, even more simplistic look,
如果更加细致地观察
we can see that each input is multiplied by its corresponding weight
我们会发现每个输入乘以对应的权重
and added at the next layer's neuron with a bias as well.
然后在下一层的神经元增加偏差
The bias is an external parameter of the neuron and can
偏差是神经元的一个外部参数
be modeled by adding an external fixed value input.
可以通过增加外部固定值输入进行建模
This entire summation will usually go through
总和一般是通过激活函数
an activation function to the next layer or to the output.
进入下一层或作为输出
But what is our goal?
不过我们的目标是什么呢？
We can look at our system as a black box that has n inputs and k outputs.
我们把系统看作黑盒子 其中包括 n 个输入 k 个输出
Our goal is to design the system in such a way that it will give us
我们的目标是通过这种方式设计系统
the correct output y for a specific input x.
这样系统可以针对特定的输入 x 提供正确的输出 y
Our job is to decide what's inside this black box.
我们的任务是决定黑盒子中的内容
We know that we will use artificial neural networks and need to train it to
我们知道可以使用人工神经网络 需要训练这个网络
eventually have a system that will yield the correct output to a specific input.
最终得到的系统可以根据特定的输入 产生正确的输出
Well, correct, most of the time.
大多数情况下这是正确的
Essentially, what we really want is to find
从本质上讲 我们实际上想要
the optimal set of weights connecting the input to the hidden layer,
找到最理想的一系列权重 把输入和隐藏层连接起来
and the optimal set of weights connecting the hidden layer to the output.
然后找到最理想的一系列权重 把隐藏层和输出连接起来
We will never have a perfect estimation,
我们永远不会得到一个完美的估值
but we can try to be as close to it as we can.
但可以无限靠近完美的估值
To do that, we need to start a process you're already familiar with,
为了做到这一点 我们需要从你已经熟悉的过程开始
and that is the training phase.
即训练阶段
So, let's look at the training phase,
那么我们来看训练阶段
where we will find the best set of weights for our system.
会发现最适合系统的一系列权重
This phase will include two steps, feedforward and backpropagation,
这个阶段包括两个步骤 前馈和反向传播
which we will repeat as many times as we need until
我们会根据需要重复多次
we decide that our system is as best as it can be.
直到确定我们的系统达到最佳效果
In the feedforward part,
在前馈部分
we will calculate the output of the system.
我们会计算系统的输出
The output will be compared to the correct output giving us an indication of the error.
对比输出和正确的输出 可以向我们提供一个误差
There are a few ways to determine the error.
确定误差的方法有好几种
We will look at it mathematically in a bit.
我们会从数学角度进行观察
In the backpropagation part,
在反向传播部分
we will change the weights as we try to minimize the error,
我们会改变权重 最小化误差
and start the feedforward process all over again.
然后不断重复前馈过程
In the next few videos,
在接下来几个视频中
we will take a closer look at
我们将细致观察
the mathematical calculations in the feedforward and the backpropagation steps.
前馈和反向传播步骤中的数学运算
We will browse through what you already know,
我们会浏览你已经了解的内容
but hopefully also give you a deeper understanding.
不过希望也能加深你的理解